Yeah, what's up guys? Wow
guy
Happier, you know, I just I trust I trust my uh, I trust my my mod to
Tell me when something's been said that they you know if enough of mods say hey, that's no because I'm just you know
People are just reporting anything. I can't you know, I'm just trying to
You know nice losing battle. I don't know. I'm just trying I'm just I'm trying to just follow the rules and like, you know
I don't have difficult rule and it's like, you know, don't stay on a live and
I'm sure you're saying something. I mean, I can't
It's hard for me to follow. You know, it's I'm trying to follow like six conversations at once and it's not always easy, right?
I'm trying best
You have more trivia, but okay, absolutely
I went to the store, grabbed a couple beers,
but guys, I don't know, wait, I'm gonna be like,
you know, I'm watching the panel.
I mean, I actually get a book,
I have a bunch of notebooks in my room.
I'm gonna bring in a notebook,
and I'm gonna start writing names down,
and there's gonna be a good list,
and then there's gonna be a naughty list,
and you're gonna wanna be on the good list,
it'll be almost as good.
Give me a, give me a link second, okay, hold on a second.
I'll give you, all of her can have the link, hold on.
But.
Joe you you stay in the chat Joe you you stay with you stay with the chat people
I'm gonna grab it. I'm gonna get a notebook. I'll be back. I'm gonna pick one out
I'm gonna get a pen hold on one second
Where's my pen?
Right there guys
You need to find a pen. Oh shit. I'm sure I have it somewhere
Hey, babe, well, I love people up. So who's backstage? Let's have a look
It's a oh bro to bring in Joe, of course Joe Joe. Just sit silently until I go over the rules. You see
You'd be your behaviors. I wish you're no Joe. Okay. No Joe be quiet people Joe Joe. Yeah
Joe's on mute for a minute. Okay, cuz I didn't explain to Joe. All right, Joe
I'm gonna keep explaining to you. There's just it's like the rules aren't hard. It's like
Everyone else can pretty much follow them. Yeah, but even people even when people make reference to the things that you're not supposed to say
It's like they say they say it again. It's like they don't understand the algorithm. It's the same thing basically, right?
Just go outside and ride your bike. Yeah, just as they go, you know, it's just like go
Yeah. Go somewhere else. Go somewhere else. Go somewhere else. Go somewhere else. Go somewhere else. Go somewhere else. Go somewhere else. Go somewhere else. Go somewhere else. Go somewhere else. Go somewhere else. Go somewhere else. Go somewhere else. Go somewhere else. Go somewhere else. Go somewhere else. Go somewhere else. Go somewhere else. Go somewhere else. Go somewhere else. Go somewhere else. Go somewhere else. Go somewhere else. Go somewhere else. Go somewhere else. Go somewhere else. Go somewhere else. Go somewhere else. Go somewhere else. Go somewhere else. Go somewhere else. Go somewhere else. Go somewhere else. Go somewhere else. Go somewhere else. Go somewhere else. Go somewhere else. Go somewhere else. Go somewhere else. Go somewhere else. Go somewhere else. Go somewhere else. Go somewhere else. Go somewhere else. Go somewhere else. Go somewhere else. Go somewhere else. Go somewhere else. Go somewhere else. Go somewhere else. Go somewhere else. Go somewhere else. Go somewhere else. Go somewhere else. Go somewhere else. Go
a good list, a naughty list.
I mean, I put like little, little,
don't write down the answers now.
I won't.
I might use the question later
and you'll have it written down.
Who is that lady on your profile picture?
Who's that lady?
Let's take a picture of me, Joe.
I'm going to be sure I'm not going to speak to this person, whoever this person is.
I'm going to be a big boy.
Let the big boys talk.
Oh, this is, I mean, Joe's harmless.
He's like, all right, what's the highest grossing film in the 80s?
How do you know all these?
I'm an 80s baby.
I already got it right Joe. How many Oscars did Raiders of the Lost part win? Not enough. Not enough. Like 20 or something? Like 20 or something?
Not 25. Not 25 Oscars. At 5. 5. 5 is true.
I was the answer.
All right, well, Lord of the Rings movie said,
what about very old friends?
When Gandalf met Bilbo, he's like,
Oh, God.
Just stop talking to me or Zildo on my pan.
I can't have talking about sex toys, please.
Anyway, guys, what do you see what I have?
I don't even interrupt all of it,
but I have this notebook I found.
I'm just going to be my show notebook.
I'm going to put all kinds of stuff in here,
but most of all, your names.
I'm gonna it serves me good pages and bad pages. I can cross out your names. I can put those
gold stars to them. It's all your choice, but look what it says in the book. It says,
be kind, right? That's like the number one rule of the show. Be kind. And I just had this notebook.
Will you make the naughty list first and put Joe on there first?
And then you draw me a bigger dick than Oliver if you draw pictures
Joe, I'm gonna I'm gonna read Joe's I'm gonna read Joe Shippley and I gotta put it
I'm gonna put a check mark next to it
My name my name is really Quincy Weberford
I thought I was like Donald Donald's like Donald Jones
What's the name of the skyscraper in the movie power
I don't know the movie diehard. Oh, I don't know the name. I don't know the
Who was in Braveheart? I don't know Gibson. No, give sir. Knock a tome plaza
I just
Yeah, he works at the what's it called? It's called like a theory fitness orange theory. I thought I thought it was it's not the one
What's that one from the like the 90s and has all pink stuff in the movie princess bride the princesses bride
Who was the I forgot I forgot who it was Robin Robin, right?
Robin Andre the Robin
Robin giant. No, it's not Robin the giant, right? I was a different
It's be the here, I love you be the baby be the I love her
Back stage when I'm last panel stop it. I'll be quiet. I'll be quiet. Okay
Wait, why did you say yes flirty what was a man? Okay, cuz his flirty time said I might do it
Question I love this trivia shit
No, but he's not gonna tell me towers to brownie. I try to hop in and say
Let's let's guess let's guess how how far down Alex James's pubes. Let's let's guess that I say I say although I say I say
You like your little land a little brass on the field, you know, so you can play ball
My god, I can respect that I can respect a little grace
the
that control somebody design goes like a clock
Yeah
Was there is somebody like putting each individual cubic here and like I'm making a real doll
guys
Trust me
Everything is perfect your brain your bones your your fucking nervous system the way you shit you have to eat everything
That's all just like no, that's like a design
Like some guys put a blueprint and was like this is how we're gonna make these assholes
Yeah, but unfortunately
But Jabroni, are you using many Manson's picture? Oh, sorry, that's Joe's picture. I'm sorry
that was a burn
It's not like
That's what just